CANDICE MARTINS

UX DESIGNER

UX Designer with a strong passion for design strategy, colour, iconography and storyboarding.

Strive to meet the user's needs by putting myself in the user's shoes, creating new ideas and solving issues that initially seem impossible.



candicem1810@gmail.com

/candicanza

/candicanza



DESIGN PROJECTS

Cakebusters

Mar 2022 - Present

UX DESIGNER

Designed a mobile app with a hassle-free pickup and delivery experience for bakery lovers where they can order online with the different payment methods and pick it up at their own convenient time or quickly get a fast delivery service.user interviews, competitive analysis, storyboarding, sketching, wireframing and prototyping using Figma.

Rebook (Reuse the book)

Jan 2022 - May 2022

UX DESIGNER

Designed a mobile app which enhanced the experience of book lovers by providing them with the unique feature of a preview video of the secondhand book before purchasing it. Conducted user interviews, user journey mapping, and heuristic evaluation and created an interactive prototype using Figma.

User Research

Persona

Story Boarding

Sketching

Wireframing

Heuristic Evalution

Prototyping



CERTIFICATES

at Designerrs Academy

Google UX Design Professional at Coursera

Mar 2022 - Present

Jan 2022 - May 2022

Figma





EDUCATION

2014 - 2019



WORK EXPERIENCES

UX UI Design from Scratch

TATA STEEL LTD, BOISAR

Jun 2021 - Feb 2022

ASSOCIATE IT

Solving the user's problems by creating new form and report per the user's requirement, working on SAP and PLSQL and debugging the Oracle forms and reports to solve the user problem.

University of Mumbai Bachelor of Computer Science

BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT EXEC E-FREEBESS PVT LTD, VIKHROLI

Jan 2021 - May 2021

Providing softwares demos for the companies listed with BSE or NSE all over India. completing the target daily by arranging the timeslots for the CA of the respective companies to join us for a demo and who is willing to purchase the software.

GRADUATE APPRENTICE

TATA STEEL LTD, BOISAR

Aug 2019 - Aug 2020

Worked on Oracle forms and report builder and created a report that would help the accounts department find the the annual cost for the entire month of the coils and provide an excel download option to that report.